http://www.encorewire.com/privacy-policy.html

Jump to Main Menu
Skip to Main Content
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests).
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer your personal information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
YOUR CONSENT
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 11/01/2008
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:
Encore Wire Corporation1329 Millwood RoadMcKinney, TX 75069supportgroup@encorewire.com
